<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Misc on ImGone98</title>
    <link>http://imgone98.com/categories/misc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Misc on ImGone98</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 15:40:46 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://imgone98.com/categories/misc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Introspection Ramblings</title>
      <link>http://imgone98.com/post/introspection/introspection-ramblings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 15:40:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://imgone98.com/post/introspection/introspection-ramblings/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Everyone has problems of some type. It&amp;rsquo;s likely that others have had very similar problems with a solution to those problems. My goal in these articles will be to tackle a problem. Solution or not. I&amp;rsquo;d like to be able to reflect on my values and goals, what I do and don&amp;rsquo;t enjoy doing, how I feel about my expectations versus reality, and my insecurities and who I am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;my-values-and-goals:5cd5e819e9cc89c145c79de1e8bad7dd&#34;&gt;My Values and Goals&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;what-i-know-i-do-and-don-t-enjoy:5cd5e819e9cc89c145c79de1e8bad7dd&#34;&gt;What I &lt;strong&gt;know&lt;/strong&gt; I Do and Don&amp;rsquo;t Enjoy&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I&amp;rsquo;ve always struggled at realizing I don&amp;rsquo;t enjoy being around certain people and what I do with those people. I&amp;rsquo;ve end up hanging with friends from a long time ago that I left for a very good reason and absolutely hating doing things with them. I was bored to death and felt like it was ruining my reputation being around them. Sadly, my inner defense mechanisms seemed to support this attitude towards hanging out with these people. I would forget to spend more time with people I do enjoy being around, or even just spending more time alone. I would hide behind my insecurities and avoid people I really do enjoy being around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;insecurities:5cd5e819e9cc89c145c79de1e8bad7dd&#34;&gt;Insecurities&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;My insecurities &lt;strong&gt;suck&lt;/strong&gt;. They literally pull me away from the people I find the most interesting out of fear that I&amp;rsquo;m not prepared for their awesomeness. Already being an socially anxious individual, most of my insecurities are detrimental to my health. They make it really hard to make new, high value friends. I will definitely write about how I plan to fix this insecurity and become a more socially acceptable human being. Of course this is me expecting this blog to help me overcome my fear of meeting really cool people and putting myself out there and exploring more opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;expectation-versus-reality:5cd5e819e9cc89c145c79de1e8bad7dd&#34;&gt;Expectation Versus Reality&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I &lt;strong&gt;hate&lt;/strong&gt; setting expectations. It&amp;rsquo;s also nearly impossible to avoid setting expectations and even more impossible to make expectations that match reality. I really want to narrow the gap between the expectations I make and what actually occurs out of those expectations. I plan to use writing as a tool to narrow that gap and get more enjoyment from controlling my expectations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I really look forward to writing about how I feel about myself and the things I accomplish. I&amp;rsquo;m almost certain I could greatly improve my life by reflecting on what works and what doesn&amp;rsquo;t. That&amp;rsquo;s exactly what the introspection category of my blog will contain and I hope it will help me build character and meet tons of cool and interesting people.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>