<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ImGone98</title>
    <link>http://imgone98.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ImGone98</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 21:56:49 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://imgone98.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Reasons I Know I am Choosing the Right Path</title>
      <link>http://imgone98.com/post/introspection/5-reasons-I-know-I-am-choosing-the-right-path/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 21:56:49 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://imgone98.com/post/introspection/5-reasons-I-know-I-am-choosing-the-right-path/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Alright, let me take a step back for a minute. I&amp;rsquo;m telling myself that I can succeed at something so many others have failed at. What makes me think I can achieve victory in this expenditure? Not to mention the fact I plan to not spend money, to hide it from family and friends and therefore receive little to no support, and .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would try to argue that this blog is for me. Well, it is. There&amp;rsquo;s really not much arguing to it. It is a blog for me. It&amp;rsquo;s is for me in the sense that I become happy when I help people with their problems and inspiring them to do amazing things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m fairly certain I&amp;rsquo;m not the only one to start a blog with those intents. I&amp;rsquo;m sure plenty have failed. So what makes me think I will succeed? My childhood fantasies, my dedication proven through education and athletic abilities, my ability to focus on the task at hand, and my understanding that I will probably never get directly paid to write these.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Obvious Nerdy Things About Me</title>
      <link>http://imgone98.com/post/nerd/5-obvious-nerdy-things-about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 17:05:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://imgone98.com/post/nerd/5-obvious-nerdy-things-about-me/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Awesome Things to Expect in my Crazy Adventures</title>
      <link>http://imgone98.com/post/adventures/5-awesome-things-to-expect-in-my-crazy-adventures/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 17:01:15 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://imgone98.com/post/adventures/5-awesome-things-to-expect-in-my-crazy-adventures/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nothing beats the thrill of standing at the top of the world as far as the eye can see. Nothing beats the thrill of mountain biking down a mountain with constant jumps and bumbs in the very narrow trail below you. Nothing beats the thrill of looking up at the biggest of cities such as New York City.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Reasons to Search for Guidance from Religion and History</title>
      <link>http://imgone98.com/post/history-religion/5-reasons-to-search-for-guidance-from-religion-and-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 17:00:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://imgone98.com/post/history-religion/5-reasons-to-search-for-guidance-from-religion-and-history/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introspection Ramblings</title>
      <link>http://imgone98.com/post/introspection/introspection-ramblings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 15:40:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://imgone98.com/post/introspection/introspection-ramblings/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Everyone has problems of some type. It&amp;rsquo;s likely that others have had very similar problems with a solution to those problems. My goal on articles in this category  will be to tackle a problem. Solution or not. I&amp;rsquo;d like to be able to reflect on my values and goals, what I do and don&amp;rsquo;t enjoy doing, how I feel about my expectations versus reality, and my insecurities and who I am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;my-values-and-goals:5cd5e819e9cc89c145c79de1e8bad7dd&#34;&gt;My Values and Goals&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obviously I have things, such as family, that are more important to me than other things. I plan to reflect on what is most important to me and how I plan to get closer to those things. I consider these values as how people view who I am. Therefore, they are very important to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am also going to evaluate how I progress in surrounding myself with my most important values. I feel this is crucial to making myself happy. If I don&amp;rsquo;t look at how achieving my goals change my life and who I am, then it will lead me down the wrong path. I will then start to live a life I don&amp;rsquo;t enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;what-i-know-i-do-and-don-t-enjoy:5cd5e819e9cc89c145c79de1e8bad7dd&#34;&gt;What I &lt;em&gt;know&lt;/em&gt; I Do and Don&amp;rsquo;t Enjoy&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve always struggled at realizing I don&amp;rsquo;t enjoy being around certain people and what I do with those people. I&amp;rsquo;ve end up hanging with friends from a long time ago that I left for a very good reason and absolutely hating doing things with them. I was bored to death and felt like it was ruining my reputation being around them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sadly, my inner defense mechanisms seemed to support this attitude towards hanging out with these people. I would forget to spend more time with people I do enjoy being around, or even just spending more time alone. I would hide behind my insecurities and avoid people I really do enjoy being around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;insecurities:5cd5e819e9cc89c145c79de1e8bad7dd&#34;&gt;Insecurities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My insecurities &lt;strong&gt;suck&lt;/strong&gt;. They literally pull me away from the people I find the most interesting out of fear that I&amp;rsquo;m not prepared for their awesomeness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Already being an socially anxious individual, most of my insecurities are detrimental to my health. They make it really hard to make new, high value friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will definitely write about how I plan to fix this insecurity and become a more socially acceptable human being. Of course this is me expecting this blog to help me overcome my fear of meeting really cool people and putting myself out there and exploring more opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;expectation-versus-reality:5cd5e819e9cc89c145c79de1e8bad7dd&#34;&gt;Expectation Versus Reality&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I &lt;strong&gt;hate&lt;/strong&gt; setting expectations. It&amp;rsquo;s also nearly impossible to avoid setting expectations and even more impossible to make expectations that match reality. I really want to narrow the gap between the expectations I make and what actually occurs out of those expectations. I plan to use writing as a tool to narrow that gap and get more enjoyment from controlling my expectations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So many subcategories fall into the introspection category of what I want to write about. For example, I could talk about my writing strategies and how I plan to strengthen them. I could write about how certain people make me feel and I how I act towards them. My habits and other important actions can fit here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really look forward to writing about how I feel about myself and the things I accomplish. I&amp;rsquo;m almost certain I could greatly improve my life by reflecting on what works and what doesn&amp;rsquo;t. That&amp;rsquo;s exactly what the introspection category of my blog will contain and I hope it will help me build character and meet tons of cool and interesting people. Most of all, I hope it helps others solve problems with their lives and gives them the right direction to a better life.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://imgone98.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2016 19:46:12 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://imgone98.com/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;*The website is mostly temporary at the moment. The blog posts will be kept, but everything else is likely to change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Welcome to the one and only Timothy Ford&amp;rsquo;s blog website! You can find my interests scattered around in four different categories found in the navigation bar at the top of the page. I feel these four different categories sum up the things I can easily talk about and share with others. They include, but aren&amp;rsquo;t limited to introspection, history and religion, nerdy stuff, and my adventures such as traveling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;1-introspection:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;1. Introspection&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;My life is filled with confusing and complicated problems constantly demanding to be solved. I mean whose life isn&amp;rsquo;t? Here is where I will put my reflections on life and explorations of what I do and don&amp;rsquo;t enjoy for the world to decipher through and maybe learn from. My goals and aspirations will also be found here. Find more about my feelings towards introspection and what can be found here at &lt;a href=&#34;http://imgone98.com/categories/post/introspection/introspection-ramblings&#34;&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;2-history-religion:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;2. History/Religion&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t say I have a strong interest in either history or religion. However, I am intrigued by how they are related and what they can teach individuals. I believe there is more to history and religion than what is taught in primary and secondary schools and should be explored as an individual more. More on what can be found here and why I find it important can be found at &lt;a href=&#34;http://imgone98.com/categories/post/history-religion/history-religion&#34;&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;3-nerdy-stuff:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;3. Nerdy Stuff&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;So many things can fit into this category I don&amp;rsquo;t even know where to start. I have many nerdy interests. I enjoy just about anything to do with a computer and can&amp;rsquo;t use the devilious Windows operating system without crying. Linux is always my go-to operating system and it fits my programming and electrical mind far more than the bloatware Microsoft offers. Games and game development can also be found here. To find out the full extent of my nerdiness look at &lt;a href=&#34;http://imgone98.com/categories/post/nerd/nerd&#34;&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;4-my-adventures:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;4. My Adventures&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;amp;nbsp&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;;I love the outdoors. Rain, snow, sleet, or hail I can be found outside running, hiking, biking, or just in general exploring the world. I plan to do some traveling one day and I have some very wierd, strong, and cheap views on living style that I wish to someday live. More information on my absurd living style and other outdoorsy things can be found at &lt;a href=&#34;http://imgone98.com/categories/post/adventures&#34;&gt;this link&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;I hope my overthought introspection ramblings, random history and religious thoughts and explorations, nerdy and scholarly writings, and my crazy adventures are entertaining and worth the read. Feel free to ask questions and write comments in the comments at the bottom of the posts. Thank you so much!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>